Mehran Beikahmadi

Software Engineer

Full Stack Developer using AI and tech skills to solve complex problems



- m_beikahmadi@shaw.ca
- Coqutilam, BC, Canada
- in linkedin.com/in/mehran-beikahmadi-99a25a110
- stackoverflow.com/users/6154396/mehranbeikahmadi

- 2365184709
- mehranbeikahmadi.github.io/Portfolio/
- github.com/mehranbeikahmadi

WORK EXPERIENCE

Sharif University of Technology Front-End Web Developer

09/2021 - Present

- Collaborated with UX/UI designers to translate design concepts into functional web interfaces
- Developed an educational website for the university using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript running on both mobile and desktop platforms
- Managed the entire Liferay DXP environment, including server configurations, user roles, and permissions

Contact: ictc.m@sharif.edu - +9821 66015363

AviHang Idea DevelopersSoftware Developer

01/2019 - 09/2021

- Collaborated with team members to deliver software solutions, including designing, coding, and testing Java applications for the company's customers
- Gained extensive programming and debugging experience developing applications using C/C++, Java, and SQL
- Develop and execute unit tests to ensure that individual components work correctly.

SUMMARY OF QUALIFICATIONS

Currently employed as a Front-End Web Developer at Sharif University of Technology

Over 8 years of experience working as a Software Developer, IT administrator, and Web Developer

MSc degree in Computer Engineering, Azad University Science and Research Branch

Strong programming and software development skills (C/C++, Python, Java, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, REACT, etc.), experience with DevOps, and Content Management Systems

Familiar with Full-stack development, Artificial Intelligence, Machine Learning, and Data Analysis

DEVELOPMENT SKILLS



PROJECTS

A Neuro-Fuzzy Model for Predicting Financial Bankruptcy in Stock Markets (12/2013 - 06/2014)

EDUCATION

Artificial Intelligence (AI)

Master of Science, Computer Engineering

09/2011 - 12/2014

- Cellular Automata
- Designing Advanced Algorithms
- Image Processing
- Neural Networks
- Evolutionary Algorithms
- Distributed Artificial Intelligence

Bachelor of Science, Computer Engineering

Azad University, Shahre Qods

09/2004 - 12/2010

- Data Structures and Algorithms
- Software Engineering
- Networking
- Computer Architecture

INTERESTS

Full-stack development

Artificial Intelligence

Machine Learning

Data Analysis